

Arjuna Panji Prakarsa

Programmer / Graphic Design

(+62) 81271310334

in linkedin.com/in/arjuna-panji-p-1b8066153

arjuna.panji97@gmail.com

https://github.com/arjunapanji21

I'm a fresh graduate from University of Dinamika Bangsa Jambi with 2 years of experience specializing in robotics and automation system. I like to think about and implement solutions to every possible problem in the world of robotics and automation system. I'm a very responsible person in terms of work, self-motivated and passionate in learning something new. My greatest strength is being a good listener, open-minded, and never give up to be a better person.



Experiences

2020-07 - Present

2020-07 - Present

2019-02 - 2020-07

2018-11 - 2019-08

2017-11 - 2018-08

2012 - 2015

2017 - 2021

2009 - 2012

2004 - 2009

2003 - 2004

Freelance Graphic Design

Specialize in Banner, Brochure and Logo Design using CorelDRAW and Photoshop

Freelance Programmer

Specialize in Python and C Programming Language for Embedded Applications

Technical Support

in Computer Laboratory of Dinamika Bangsa University

Main Programmer and Team Leader

of Dinamika Bangsa University in Indonesian Robotic Contest 2019

Additional Programmer

of Dinamika Bangsa University in Indonesian Robotic Contest 2018

Educations

BS in Computer Science University of Dinamika Bangsa Jambi, Indonesia.

- Graduated Cum Laude with GPA 3.93/4
- Computer Laboratory Assistant
- Leader of Robotic Club

Vocational High School #2 Jambi City, Indonesia.

- Department of Multimedia

Junior High School #10 Jambi City, Indonesia.

- Member of IT Departement

Elementary School #8 Jambi City, Indonesia.

Elementary School #205 Jambi City, Indonesia.



Skills

þ	Python	000000000	10/10
þ	С	•••••••	8/10
þ	C#	••••••	7/10
þ	PHP	••••••	6/10
þ	Linux	000000000	10/10
þ	CorelDRAW	000000000	9/10
þ	Photoshop	000000000	9/10
Q	Microsoft Office	000000000	8/10



Languages

	Indonesian	10/10
	English	8/10
þ	Japanese	5/10